[{"id":1,"question":"How many teams play in NFL","answer":["30","32","34","28"],"corectAnswer":"32","diff":1},{"id":2,"question":"In how many divisions NFL teams are divided?","answer":["2","4","8","10"],"corectAnswer":"8","diff":1},{"id":3,"question":"In which season the first Super Bowl was played?","answer":["1964","1965","31961","1966"],"corectAnswer":"1966","diff":2},{"id":4,"question":"Who won Super Bowl I?","answer":["Green Bay Packers","Dallas Cowboys","Pittsburgh Steelers","Kansas City Chiefs"],"corectAnswer":"Green Bay Packers","diff":1},{"id":5,"question":"How many points is Touchdown?","answer":["1","3","6","7"],"corectAnswer":"6","diff":1},{"id":6,"question":"How many NFL teams are seated in Texas?","answer":["1","2","3","4"],"corectAnswer":"2","diff":1},{"id":7,"question":"Black and silver are colors of which team?","answer":["Raiders","49ers","Giants","Texans"],"corectAnswer":"Raiders","diff":1},{"id":8,"question":"Youngest franchise in NFL?","answer":["Tampa Bay Buccaneers","Tennessee Titans","St Louis Rams","Houston Texans"],"corectAnswer":"Houston Texans","diff":1},{"id":9,"question":"Which team is seated in Jacksonvile?","answer":["Jaguars","Eagles","Seahawks","Rams"],"corectAnswer":"Jaguars","diff":1},{"id":10,"question":"In which town Tennessee Titans play their home games?","answer":["Chicago","Atlanta","Baltimore","Nashville"],"corectAnswer":"Nashville","diff":2},{"id":11,"question":"Legend Joe Montana played for?","answer":["Miami Dolphins","Dallas Cowboys","San Francisco 49ers","New England Patriots"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":1},{"id":12,"question":"Legend Tom Landry was head coach of which team?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Philadelphia Eagles","Washington Redskins","Seattle Seahawks"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":1},{"id":13,"question":"Legend Joe Namath played for?","answer":["Minnesota Vikings","Buffalo Bills","Pittsburgh Steelers","New York Jets"],"corectAnswer":"New York Jets","diff":1},{"id":14,"question":"Legend Walter Payton played for?","answer":["Cincinnati Bengals","Chicago Bears","Cleveland Browns","Indianapolis Colts"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":1},{"id":15,"question":"Legend Vince Lombardi was head coach of which team?","answer":["Denver Broncos","Arizona Cardinals","Green Bay Packers","Miami Dolphins"],"corectAnswer":"Green Bay Packers","diff":1},{"id":16,"question":"Legend Dan Marino played for?","answer":["Miami Dolphins","San Diego Chargers","New Orleans Saints","San Francisco 49ers"],"corectAnswer":"Miami Dolphins","diff":1},{"id":17,"question":"Legend Jerry Rice played for?","answer":["San Francisco 49ers","Atlanta Falcons","Carolina Panthers","Kansas City Chiefs"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":1},{"id":18,"question":"Legend Steve Young played for?","answer":["Washington Redskins","Pittsburgh Steelers","Philadelphia Eagles","San Francisco 49ers"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":1},{"id":19,"question":"Legend Terry Bradshaw played for?","answer":["Pittsburgh Steelers","Oakland Raiders","Cleveland Browns","Bufallo Bills"],"corectAnswer":"Pittsburgh Steelers","diff":2},{"id":20,"question":"Legend Jimmy Johnson was head coach of which team?","answer":["Atlanta Falcons","St. Louis Rams","Dallas Cowboys","New England Patriots"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":2},{"id":21,"question":"Legend Dick Butkus played for?","answer":["Tennessee Titans","Chicago Bears","San Diego Chargers","Indianapolis Colts"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":2},{"id":22,"question":"Legend Lawrence Taylor played for?","answer":["New York Giants","Tampa Bay Buccaneers","Oakland Raiders","Buffalo Bills"],"corectAnswer":"New York Giants","diff":2},{"id":23,"question":"Legend Jim Brown played for?","answer":["Minnesota Vikings","Cleveland Browns","Jacksonville Jaguars","Denver Broncos"],"corectAnswer":"Cleveland Browns","diff":1},{"id":24,"question":"Legend Ray Lewis played for?","answer":["Tennessee Titans","Chicago Bears","Baltimore Ravens","Arizona Cardinals"],"corectAnswer":"Baltimore Ravens","diff":1},{"id":25,"question":"Legend Michael Irwin played for?","answer":["Washington Redskins","New England Patriots","San Francisco 49ers","Dallas Cowboys"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":2},{"id":26,"question":"Legend Fran Tarkenton played for?","answer":["Philadelphia Eagles","Minnesota Vikings","Miami Dolphins","Atlanta Falcons"],"corectAnswer":"Minnesota Vikings","diff":3},{"id":27,"question":"Legend Troy Aikman played for?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Cleveland Browns","Kansas City Chiefs","Seattle Seahawks"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":2},{"id":28,"question":"Legend Bobby Bell played for?","answer":["Green Bay Packers","New York Jets","Oakland Raiders","Kansas City Chiefs"],"corectAnswer":"Kansas City Chiefs","diff":3},{"id":29,"question":"Legend Willie Brown played for?","answer":["Oakland Raiders","Pittsburgh Steelers","Buffalo Bills","New Orleans Saints"],"corectAnswer":"Oakland Raiders","diff":3},{"id":30,"question":"Legend Jim Otto played for?","answer":["San Francisco 49ers","Chicago Bears","Oakland Raiders","Cincinnati Bengals"],"corectAnswer":"Oakland Raiders","diff":2},{"id":31,"question":"Legend Steve Van Buren played for?","answer":["Philadelphia Eagles","St. Louis Rams","San Diego Chargers","Carolina Panthers"],"corectAnswer":"Philadelphia Eagles","diff":3},{"id":32,"question":"Legend Mike Singletary played for?","answer":["San Francisco 49ers","Chicago Bears","Buffalo Bills","Indianapolis Colts"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":3},{"id":33,"question":"Legend Gene Upshaw played for?","answer":["New York Giants","New Orleans Saints","Seattle Seahawks","Oakland Raiders"],"corectAnswer":"Oakland Raiders","diff":2},{"id":34,"question":"Legend Willie Lanier played for?","answer":["Kansas City Chiefs","Jacsonville Jaguars","Baltimore Ravens","Tennessee Titans"],"corectAnswer":"Kansas City Chiefs","diff":3},{"id":35,"question":"Legend Bart Starr played for?","answer":["Arizona Cardinals","Washington Redskins","Tampa Bay Bucckaneers","Green Bay Packers"],"corectAnswer":"Green Bay Packers","diff":3},{"id":36,"question":"Legend Roger Staubach played for?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","St. Louis Rams","New York Jets","New York Giants"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":2},{"id":37,"question":"Legend Jack Lambert played for?","answer":["New Orleans Saints","Pittsburgh Steelers","Buffalo Bills","Carolina Panthers"],"corectAnswer":"Pittsburgh Steelers","diff":2},{"id":38,"question":"Legend Emmitt Smith played for?","answer":["Cincinnati Bengals","Atlanta Falcons","New England Patriots","Dallas Cowboys"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":1},{"id":39,"question":"Legend Jon Elway played for?","answer":["San Francisco 49ers","Denver Broncos","Miami Dolphins","Cincinnati Bengals"],"corectAnswer":"Denver Broncos","diff":2},{"id":40,"question":"Legend Brett Favre played for?","answer":["Arizona Cardinals","Baltimore Ravens","Green Bay Packers","St. Louis Rams"],"corectAnswer":"Green Bay Packers","diff":1},{"id":41,"question":"Legend Barry Sanders played for?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Detroit Lions","New York Giants","Indianapolis Colts"],"corectAnswer":"Detroit Lions","diff":2},{"id":42,"question":"Legend Otto Graham played for?","answer":["Detroit Lions","New England Patriots","Seattle Seahawks","Cleveland Browns"],"corectAnswer":"Cleveland Browns","diff":30},{"id":43,"question":"Legend Joe Greene played for?","answer":["Pittsburgh Steelers","Chicago Bears","Baltimore Ravens","New York Jets"],"corectAnswer":"Pittsburgh Steelers","diff":2},{"id":44,"question":"Legend Bill Walsh was head coach of which team?","answer":["Atlanta Falcons","Green Bay Packers","Jacksonville Jaguars","San Francisco 49ers"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":1},{"id":45,"question":"Legend Chuck Noll was head coach of which team?","answer":["New Orleans Saints","Pittsburgh Steelers","Detroit Lions","Miami Dolphins"],"corectAnswer":"Pittsburgh Steelers","diff":2},{"id":46,"question":"Legend Mike Ditka was head coach of which team?","answer":["Detroi Lions","Baltimore Ravens","Buffalo Bills","Chicago Bears"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":2},{"id":47,"question":"Legend John Madden was head coach of which team?","answer":["San Francisco 49ers","Oakland Raiders","Minnesota Vikings","New England Patriots"],"corectAnswer":"Oakland Raiders","diff":2},{"id":48,"question":"Legend Joe Gibbs was head coach of which team?","answer":["Washington Redskins","Carolina Panthers","Detroit Lions","Cleveland Browns"],"corectAnswer":"Washington Redskins","diff":3},{"id":49,"question":"Legend Don Shula was head coach of which team?","answer":["Tampa Bay Buccaneers","Kansas City Chiefs","Miami Dolphins","Seattle Seahawks"],"corectAnswer":"Miami Dolphins","diff":2},{"id":50,"question":"Legend George Halas was head coach of which team?","answer":["Chicago Bears","St. Louis Rams","New Orleans Saints","Detroit Lions"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":3},{"id":51,"question":"Legend Marv Levy was head coach of which team?","answer":["Carolina Panthers","New England Patriots","Cincinnati Bengals","Buffalo Bills"],"corectAnswer":"Buffalo Bills","diff":2},{"id":52,"question":"Legend Bud Grant was head coach of which team?","answer":["Minnesota Vikings","St. Louis Rams","New York Jets","Detroit Lions"],"corectAnswer":"Minnesota Vikings","diff":3},{"id":53,"question":"How long is quarter in NFL game?","answer":["10min.","12min.","15min.","20min."],"corectAnswer":"15min","diff":1},{"id":54,"question":"How long is halftime in NFL game?","answer":["10min.","12min.","15min.","20min."],"corectAnswer":"12min","diff":2},{"id":55,"question":"Who plays home games at Bank of America stadium?","answer":["New England Patriots","Arizona Cardinals","Jacksonville Jaguars","Carolina Panthers"],"corectAnswer":"Carolina Panthers","diff":3},{"id":56,"question":"Who plays home games at University of Phoenix stadium?","answer":["Arizona Cardinals","Seattle Seahawks","Baltimore Ravens","New York Giants"],"corectAnswer":"Arizona Cardinals","diff":3},{"id":57,"question":"Who plays home games at Lambeau Field stadium?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Green Bay Packers","San Francisco 49ers","Kanzas City Chiefs"],"corectAnswer":"Green Bay Packers","diff":3},{"id":58,"question":"Who plays home games at CenturyLink stadium?","answer":["Miami Dolphins","Buffalo Bills","Seattle Seahawks","New York Jets"],"corectAnswer":"Seattle Seahawks","diff":3},{"id":59,"question":"Who plays home games at Soldier Field stadium?","answer":["Chicago Bears","Dallas Cowboys","St. Louis Rams","Minnesota Vikings"],"corectAnswer":"Chicago Bears","diff":3},{"id":60,"question":"Who plays home games at Ford Field stadium?","answer":["New England Patriots","Indianapolis Colts","Detroit Lions","Tennessee Titans"],"corectAnswer":"Detroit Lions","diff":3},{"id":61,"question":"Gold Rush are which team cheerleaders?","answer":["Kansas City Chiefs","San Francisco 49ers","Chicago Bears","New Orleans Saints"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":3},{"id":62,"question":"America's Sweethears are which team cheerleaders?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Miami Dolphins","New York Giants","Arizona Cardinals"],"corectAnswer":"Dallas Cowboys","diff":3},{"id":63,"question":"TopCats are which team cheerleaders?","answer":["Cincinnati Bengals","Carolina Panthers","New York Jets","Houston Texans"],"corectAnswer":"Carolina Panthers","diff":3},{"id":64,"question":"Sea Gals are which team cheerleaders?","answer":["Miami Dolphins","Oakland Riders","New Orleans Saints","Seattle Seahawks"],"corectAnswer":"Seattle Seahawks","diff":3},{"id":65,"question":"SwashBucklers are which team cheerleaders?","answer":["Houston Texans","St. Louis Rams","Tampa Bay Buccaneers","Detroit Lions"],"corectAnswer":"Tampa Bay Buccaneers","diff":3},{"id":66,"question":"How many officials are on the field during an NFL game?","answer":["3","5","7","10"],"corectAnswer":"7","diff":3},{"id":67,"question":"How many players on roster can NFL team have?","answer":["25","45","48","53"],"corectAnswer":"53","diff":2},{"id":68,"question":"Edward J. DeBartolo, Jr. was owner of which NFL franchise?","answer":["Dallas Cowboys","Jackosville Jaguars","San Francisco 49ers","Chicago Bears"],"corectAnswer":"San Francisco 49ers","diff":3},{"id":69,"question":"Al Davis was owner of which NFL franchise?","answer":["Oakland Raiders","Green Bay Packers","Buffalo Bills","Arizona Cardinals"],"corectAnswer":"Oakland Riders","diff":2},{"id":70,"question":"Tim Mara was owner of which NFL franchise?","answer":["St. Louis Rams","New England Patriots","Indianapolis Colts","New York Giants"],"corectAnswer":"New York Giants","diff":2}]